Closer - The Chainsmokers&Halsey
[00:10.07]
Hey I was doing just fine before I met you
I drink too much and that's an issue but I'm okay
在遇见你之前 我一切都好
Hey you tell your friends it was nice to meet them
我有点醉 这是个问题 但我还好
But I hope I never see them again
嘿 你告诉你的朋友们 很开心跟他们碰面
I know it breaks your heart
但我希望我能与他们不再相见
I moved to the city in a broke down car and
我知道这会让你很受伤
Four years no call
开着辆老爷车搬进市区
Now you're looking pretty in a hotel bar and
四年了没有一通电话
I can't stop
如今坐在酒吧区的你是那么惊艳
No I can't stop
我情不自禁
So baby pull me closer in the backseat of your rover
不 我情不自禁走向你
That I know you can't afford
亲爱的 在你的罗孚车后座让我更靠近你些吧
Bite that tattoo on your shoulder
我知道你买不起
Pull the sheets right off the corner
咬咬你肩膀上的纹身
Of the mattress that you stole
将你从波兰室友那里
From your roommate back in boland
偷来的床垫角落的被单
We ain't ever getting older
盖到我身上
我们绝不会老去
We ain't ever getting older
Look as good as the day I met you
我们绝不会老去
I forgot just why I left you
你依然是我们初次邂逅那样美丽
I was insane
我都忘了为何曾经我会离开你
Stay take up pink lady to song
我一定是疯了
That we beat it that we to song OK
伴着歌声啜饮着鸡尾酒
I know it breaks your heart
我们随着旋律摇摆
I moved to the city in a broke down car and
我知道这会让你很受伤
Four years no call
开着辆老爷车搬进市区
Now you're looking pretty in a hotel bar and
四年了没有一通电话
I can't stop
如今坐在酒吧区的你是那么惊艳
No I can't stop
我情不自禁
So baby pull me closer in the backseat of your rover
不 我情不自禁走向你
That I know you can't afford
亲爱的 在你的罗孚车后座让我更靠近你些吧
Bite that tattoo on your shoulder
我知道你买不起
Pull the sheets right off the corner
咬咬你肩膀上的纹身
Of the mattress that you stole
将你从波兰室友那里
From your roommate back in boland
偷来的床垫角落的被单
We ain't ever getting older
盖到我身上
我们绝不会老去
We ain't ever getting older
So baby pull me closer in the backseat of your rover
我们绝不会老去
That I know you can't afford
亲爱的 在你的罗孚车后座让我更靠近你些吧
Bite that tattoo on your shoulder
我知道你买不起
Pull the sheets right off the corner
咬咬你肩膀上的纹身
Of the mattress that you stole
将你从波兰室友那里
From your roommate back in boland
偷来的床垫角落的被单
We ain't ever getting older
盖到我身上
我们绝不会老去
We ain't ever getting older
[03:55.09]
我们绝不会老去